The implication of a secret space program.
Above Majestic is a documentary film directed by Roger R. Richards.
A look at the origins, history and conspiracies behind the "Majestic 12", a clandestine group of military
and corporate figureheads charged with reverse-engineering extraterrestrial technology.
Self, played by John DeSouza.
Self, played by Laura Magdelene Eisenhower.
Self, played by Corey Goode.
Self, played by Michael Salla.
Self, played by Jordan Sather.
Self, played by William Tompkins.
Above Majestic is a 2018 documentary film that posits a global conspiracy involving
anthropomorphic alien reptiles who secretly control the world's governments.
The film was the most successful documentary of 2018 on iTunes.
According to Vice, Above Majestic advances the theory that "reptilian aliens occupy large swaths of
Antarctica, are massing for an invasion, and control the world’s governments and banks".
The documentary also makes the case that the September 11 attacks were
a purported attempt to conceal an alien conspiracy.
In 2021, researchers at Logically reported that the person operating the influential,
QAnon-linked Twitter handle qthewakeup may have assisted in the filming of the documentary.